<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.8.5">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2020-03-05T09:05:36-08:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Huma(N)ature</title><subtitle>Write an awesome description for your new site here. You can edit this line in _config.yml. It will appear in your document head meta (for Google search results) and in your feed.xml site description.</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Sun, Mar 15, 7PM</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2020/03/15/1.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Sun, Mar 15, 7PM" /><published>2020-03-15T20:00:00-07:00</published><updated>2020-03-15T20:00:00-07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2020/03/15/1</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2020/03/15/1.html">&lt;center&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Dispatches from the Great Burning: What My Mennonite Ancestors and the Gobi Bear Taught Me About Surviving the Climate Emergency&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/center&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;by Helen Stoltzfus&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;Sunday, March 8th, 4pm; and Sunday, March 15th, 7pm&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Dispatches from the Great Burning: What My Mennonite Ancestors and the Gobi Bear Taught Me About Surviving the Climate Emergency by Helen Stoltzfus&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What does it mean to be a worthy ancestor – or a worthy human being – in a time of catastrophic upheaval? What does it mean to act audaciously – without knowing the outcome of one’s actions? One woman, six dispatches from: The Gobi Desert of Mongolia. The Big Bang. The Civil War. Oakland. The Alaskan tundra. Paradise…and its fires.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div style=&quot;text-align: center;&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://localhost:4000/img/climateemergency.jpeg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;center&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Siren's last song&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/center&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;by Ebb/Flow Collective&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;Saturday, March 7th, 8pm&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Ocean herself brings an oil-slicked message with the tide.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rainbow plastics fill the siren’s tail as he swims a somber finale, alone in a foreign place he once called home.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The siren’s last song, a distant memory –the Ocean embraces him as he drifts into eternal sleep.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div style=&quot;text-align: center;&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://localhost:4000/img/sirensong.jpeg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;center&gt;&lt;h3&gt;The Secrets Of The Trees&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/center&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;by Caitlyn Kilgore; featuring Stephanie Chen, Bobbi Dulaney, Carrie Gaydos, and Mel Mark&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;All Dates and Times&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Inspired by the book The Hidden Life of Trees by Peter Wohleben, this piece blossomed into an affirmation of our interdependence. Drawing inspiration from Standing Rock and other political actions, and books like Blessed Unrest and Radical Ecology, the performers have woven together a story of struggle and hope in a harrowing time. Touching on themes of socialism, competition, set-back, and rebirth, The Secrets of the Trees is a circus, dance, and theatrical critique of capitalism and greed told through the eyes of the forest as they struggle for survival in the Anthropocene.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div style=&quot;text-align: center;&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://localhost:4000/img/secretofthetrees.jpeg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Dispatches from the Great Burning: What My Mennonite Ancestors and the Gobi Bear Taught Me About Surviving the Climate Emergency by Helen Stoltzfus Sunday, March 8th, 4pm; and Sunday, March 15th, 7pm Dispatches from the Great Burning: What My Mennonite Ancestors and the Gobi Bear Taught Me About Surviving the Climate Emergency by Helen Stoltzfus What does it mean to be a worthy ancestor – or a worthy human being – in a time of catastrophic upheaval? What does it mean to act audaciously – without knowing the outcome of one’s actions? One woman, six dispatches from: The Gobi Desert of Mongolia. The Big Bang. The Civil War. Oakland. The Alaskan tundra. Paradise…and its fires. Siren's last song by Ebb/Flow Collective Saturday, March 7th, 8pm The Ocean herself brings an oil-slicked message with the tide. Rainbow plastics fill the siren’s tail as he swims a somber finale, alone in a foreign place he once called home. The siren’s last song, a distant memory –the Ocean embraces him as he drifts into eternal sleep. The Secrets Of The Trees by Caitlyn Kilgore; featuring Stephanie Chen, Bobbi Dulaney, Carrie Gaydos, and Mel Mark All Dates and Times Inspired by the book The Hidden Life of Trees by Peter Wohleben, this piece blossomed into an affirmation of our interdependence. Drawing inspiration from Standing Rock and other political actions, and books like Blessed Unrest and Radical Ecology, the performers have woven together a story of struggle and hope in a harrowing time. Touching on themes of socialism, competition, set-back, and rebirth, The Secrets of the Trees is a circus, dance, and theatrical critique of capitalism and greed told through the eyes of the forest as they struggle for survival in the Anthropocene.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Sat, Mar 14, 8PM</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2020/03/14/1.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Sat, Mar 14, 8PM" /><published>2020-03-14T20:00:00-07:00</published><updated>2020-03-14T20:00:00-07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2020/03/14/1</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2020/03/14/1.html">&lt;center&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Cancel the Apocalypse&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/center&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;by Big Drama No Drama&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;Friday, March 13th, 8pm; and Saturday, March 14th, 8pm&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Cancel the Apocalypse is a new work of experimental music-theatre by East Bay-based performance group Big Drama No Drama. This avant-rock opera conjures the overdriven angst of our hypermodern moment through song, soundscape, spoken word, and movement. Two musician-actors, Daniel Larlham and Liz DeRoche, offer up a screwball diagnosis of a culture in turmoil, as the production moves from a focus on the personal microcosm (disheartenment, confusion, despair) to a reckoning with the macrocosmic crisis of climate change. Audiences will take away from the production an infusion of vitality and hope, a realistic sense of faith in the resilience of life as an antidote to the seduction of doomsday thinking.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div style=&quot;text-align: center;&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://localhost:4000/img/cancelled.jpeg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;center&gt;&lt;h3&gt;The Secrets Of The Trees&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/center&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;by Caitlyn Kilgore; featuring Stephanie Chen, Bobbi Dulaney, Carrie Gaydos, and Mel Mark&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;All Dates and Times&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Inspired by the book The Hidden Life of Trees by Peter Wohleben, this piece blossomed into an affirmation of our interdependence. Drawing inspiration from Standing Rock and other political actions, and books like Blessed Unrest and Radical Ecology, the performers have woven together a story of struggle and hope in a harrowing time. Touching on themes of socialism, competition, set-back, and rebirth, The Secrets of the Trees is a circus, dance, and theatrical critique of capitalism and greed told through the eyes of the forest as they struggle for survival in the Anthropocene.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div style=&quot;text-align: center;&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://localhost:4000/img/secretofthetrees.jpeg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Cancel the Apocalypse by Big Drama No Drama Friday, March 13th, 8pm; and Saturday, March 14th, 8pm Cancel the Apocalypse is a new work of experimental music-theatre by East Bay-based performance group Big Drama No Drama. This avant-rock opera conjures the overdriven angst of our hypermodern moment through song, soundscape, spoken word, and movement. Two musician-actors, Daniel Larlham and Liz DeRoche, offer up a screwball diagnosis of a culture in turmoil, as the production moves from a focus on the personal microcosm (disheartenment, confusion, despair) to a reckoning with the macrocosmic crisis of climate change. Audiences will take away from the production an infusion of vitality and hope, a realistic sense of faith in the resilience of life as an antidote to the seduction of doomsday thinking. The Secrets Of The Trees by Caitlyn Kilgore; featuring Stephanie Chen, Bobbi Dulaney, Carrie Gaydos, and Mel Mark All Dates and Times Inspired by the book The Hidden Life of Trees by Peter Wohleben, this piece blossomed into an affirmation of our interdependence. Drawing inspiration from Standing Rock and other political actions, and books like Blessed Unrest and Radical Ecology, the performers have woven together a story of struggle and hope in a harrowing time. Touching on themes of socialism, competition, set-back, and rebirth, The Secrets of the Trees is a circus, dance, and theatrical critique of capitalism and greed told through the eyes of the forest as they struggle for survival in the Anthropocene.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Fri, Mar 13, 8PM</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2020/03/13/1.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Fri, Mar 13, 8PM" /><published>2020-03-13T20:00:00-07:00</published><updated>2020-03-13T20:00:00-07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2020/03/13/1</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2020/03/13/1.html">&lt;center&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Cancel the Apocalypse&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/center&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;by Big Drama No Drama&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;Friday, March 13th, 8pm; and Saturday, March 14th, 8pm&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Cancel the Apocalypse is a new work of experimental music-theatre by East Bay-based performance group Big Drama No Drama. This avant-rock opera conjures the overdriven angst of our hypermodern moment through song, soundscape, spoken word, and movement. Two musician-actors, Daniel Larlham and Liz DeRoche, offer up a screwball diagnosis of a culture in turmoil, as the production moves from a focus on the personal microcosm (disheartenment, confusion, despair) to a reckoning with the macrocosmic crisis of climate change. Audiences will take away from the production an infusion of vitality and hope, a realistic sense of faith in the resilience of life as an antidote to the seduction of doomsday thinking.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div style=&quot;text-align: center;&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://localhost:4000/img/cancelled.jpeg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;center&gt;&lt;h3&gt;The Secrets Of The Trees&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/center&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;by Caitlyn Kilgore; featuring Stephanie Chen, Bobbi Dulaney, Carrie Gaydos, and Mel Mark&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;All Dates and Times&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Inspired by the book The Hidden Life of Trees by Peter Wohleben, this piece blossomed into an affirmation of our interdependence. Drawing inspiration from Standing Rock and other political actions, and books like Blessed Unrest and Radical Ecology, the performers have woven together a story of struggle and hope in a harrowing time. Touching on themes of socialism, competition, set-back, and rebirth, The Secrets of the Trees is a circus, dance, and theatrical critique of capitalism and greed told through the eyes of the forest as they struggle for survival in the Anthropocene.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div style=&quot;text-align: center;&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://localhost:4000/img/secretofthetrees.jpeg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Cancel the Apocalypse by Big Drama No Drama Friday, March 13th, 8pm; and Saturday, March 14th, 8pm Cancel the Apocalypse is a new work of experimental music-theatre by East Bay-based performance group Big Drama No Drama. This avant-rock opera conjures the overdriven angst of our hypermodern moment through song, soundscape, spoken word, and movement. Two musician-actors, Daniel Larlham and Liz DeRoche, offer up a screwball diagnosis of a culture in turmoil, as the production moves from a focus on the personal microcosm (disheartenment, confusion, despair) to a reckoning with the macrocosmic crisis of climate change. Audiences will take away from the production an infusion of vitality and hope, a realistic sense of faith in the resilience of life as an antidote to the seduction of doomsday thinking. The Secrets Of The Trees by Caitlyn Kilgore; featuring Stephanie Chen, Bobbi Dulaney, Carrie Gaydos, and Mel Mark All Dates and Times Inspired by the book The Hidden Life of Trees by Peter Wohleben, this piece blossomed into an affirmation of our interdependence. Drawing inspiration from Standing Rock and other political actions, and books like Blessed Unrest and Radical Ecology, the performers have woven together a story of struggle and hope in a harrowing time. Touching on themes of socialism, competition, set-back, and rebirth, The Secrets of the Trees is a circus, dance, and theatrical critique of capitalism and greed told through the eyes of the forest as they struggle for survival in the Anthropocene.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Thu, Mar 12, 8PM</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2020/03/12/1.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Thu, Mar 12, 8PM" /><published>2020-03-12T20:00:00-07:00</published><updated>2020-03-12T20:00:00-07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2020/03/12/1</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2020/03/12/1.html">&lt;center&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Upwelling&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/center&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;www.nommensendance.com&quot;&gt;by Nommensen Dance&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;Thursday, March 12th, 8pm&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Upwelling” is a ocean-inspired dance performance created by Amelia Nommensen in collaboration with dancers Chelsea Boyd Brown, Annalise Constantz, Wednesday Manners and original cast member Audrey Johnson. This work in progress takes a dive into the alluring mysteries of the ocean with underwater recordings, poetry, song, and modern dance exploring the strength of feminine forces. With an original sound score by Joe Krempetz, allow the auditory and visual journey to leave your heart full of wonder and with the impulse to save our seas.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div style=&quot;text-align: center;&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://localhost:4000/img/upwelling.jpeg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;center&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Out of the Dust&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/center&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;by Kirstin Brown and Helen Fitanides&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;Saturday, March 7th, 8pm; and Thursday, March 12th, 8pm&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Out of the Dust explores the fate of creatures living in a world in which they can no longer survive. Starting on the ground, they are forced to adapt to environmental factors outside their control, and eventually must find new habitat for their species survival. This piece embodies the struggle of all beings facing a changing climate and limited resources.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;center&gt;&lt;h3&gt;The Secrets Of The Trees&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/center&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;by Caitlyn Kilgore; featuring Stephanie Chen, Bobbi Dulaney, Carrie Gaydos, and Mel Mark&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;All Dates and Times&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Inspired by the book The Hidden Life of Trees by Peter Wohleben, this piece blossomed into an affirmation of our interdependence. Drawing inspiration from Standing Rock and other political actions, and books like Blessed Unrest and Radical Ecology, the performers have woven together a story of struggle and hope in a harrowing time. Touching on themes of socialism, competition, set-back, and rebirth, The Secrets of the Trees is a circus, dance, and theatrical critique of capitalism and greed told through the eyes of the forest as they struggle for survival in the Anthropocene.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div style=&quot;text-align: center;&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://localhost:4000/img/secretofthetrees.jpeg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Upwelling by Nommensen Dance Thursday, March 12th, 8pm “Upwelling” is a ocean-inspired dance performance created by Amelia Nommensen in collaboration with dancers Chelsea Boyd Brown, Annalise Constantz, Wednesday Manners and original cast member Audrey Johnson. This work in progress takes a dive into the alluring mysteries of the ocean with underwater recordings, poetry, song, and modern dance exploring the strength of feminine forces. With an original sound score by Joe Krempetz, allow the auditory and visual journey to leave your heart full of wonder and with the impulse to save our seas. Out of the Dust by Kirstin Brown and Helen Fitanides Saturday, March 7th, 8pm; and Thursday, March 12th, 8pm Out of the Dust explores the fate of creatures living in a world in which they can no longer survive. Starting on the ground, they are forced to adapt to environmental factors outside their control, and eventually must find new habitat for their species survival. This piece embodies the struggle of all beings facing a changing climate and limited resources. The Secrets Of The Trees by Caitlyn Kilgore; featuring Stephanie Chen, Bobbi Dulaney, Carrie Gaydos, and Mel Mark All Dates and Times Inspired by the book The Hidden Life of Trees by Peter Wohleben, this piece blossomed into an affirmation of our interdependence. Drawing inspiration from Standing Rock and other political actions, and books like Blessed Unrest and Radical Ecology, the performers have woven together a story of struggle and hope in a harrowing time. Touching on themes of socialism, competition, set-back, and rebirth, The Secrets of the Trees is a circus, dance, and theatrical critique of capitalism and greed told through the eyes of the forest as they struggle for survival in the Anthropocene.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Sun, Mar 8, 4PM</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2020/03/08/2.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Sun, Mar 8, 4PM" /><published>2020-03-08T16:00:00-07:00</published><updated>2020-03-08T16:00:00-07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2020/03/08/2</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2020/03/08/2.html">&lt;center&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Dispatches from the Great Burning: What My Mennonite Ancestors and the Gobi Bear Taught Me About Surviving the Climate Emergency&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/center&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;by Helen Stoltzfus&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;Sunday, March 8th, 4pm; and Sunday, March 15th, 7pm&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Dispatches from the Great Burning: What My Mennonite Ancestors and the Gobi Bear Taught Me About Surviving the Climate Emergency by Helen Stoltzfus&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What does it mean to be a worthy ancestor – or a worthy human being – in a time of catastrophic upheaval? What does it mean to act audaciously – without knowing the outcome of one’s actions? One woman, six dispatches from: The Gobi Desert of Mongolia. The Big Bang. The Civil War. Oakland. The Alaskan tundra. Paradise…and its fires.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div style=&quot;text-align: center;&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://localhost:4000/img/climateemergency.jpeg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;center&gt;&lt;h3&gt;The Secrets Of The Trees&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/center&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;by Caitlyn Kilgore; featuring Stephanie Chen, Bobbi Dulaney, Carrie Gaydos, and Mel Mark&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;All Dates and Times&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Inspired by the book The Hidden Life of Trees by Peter Wohleben, this piece blossomed into an affirmation of our interdependence. Drawing inspiration from Standing Rock and other political actions, and books like Blessed Unrest and Radical Ecology, the performers have woven together a story of struggle and hope in a harrowing time. Touching on themes of socialism, competition, set-back, and rebirth, The Secrets of the Trees is a circus, dance, and theatrical critique of capitalism and greed told through the eyes of the forest as they struggle for survival in the Anthropocene.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div style=&quot;text-align: center;&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://localhost:4000/img/secretofthetrees.jpeg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Dispatches from the Great Burning: What My Mennonite Ancestors and the Gobi Bear Taught Me About Surviving the Climate Emergency by Helen Stoltzfus Sunday, March 8th, 4pm; and Sunday, March 15th, 7pm Dispatches from the Great Burning: What My Mennonite Ancestors and the Gobi Bear Taught Me About Surviving the Climate Emergency by Helen Stoltzfus What does it mean to be a worthy ancestor – or a worthy human being – in a time of catastrophic upheaval? What does it mean to act audaciously – without knowing the outcome of one’s actions? One woman, six dispatches from: The Gobi Desert of Mongolia. The Big Bang. The Civil War. Oakland. The Alaskan tundra. Paradise…and its fires. The Secrets Of The Trees by Caitlyn Kilgore; featuring Stephanie Chen, Bobbi Dulaney, Carrie Gaydos, and Mel Mark All Dates and Times Inspired by the book The Hidden Life of Trees by Peter Wohleben, this piece blossomed into an affirmation of our interdependence. Drawing inspiration from Standing Rock and other political actions, and books like Blessed Unrest and Radical Ecology, the performers have woven together a story of struggle and hope in a harrowing time. Touching on themes of socialism, competition, set-back, and rebirth, The Secrets of the Trees is a circus, dance, and theatrical critique of capitalism and greed told through the eyes of the forest as they struggle for survival in the Anthropocene.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Sat, Mar 7, 8PM</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2020/03/07/1.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Sat, Mar 7, 8PM" /><published>2020-03-07T20:00:00-08:00</published><updated>2020-03-07T20:00:00-08:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2020/03/07/1</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2020/03/07/1.html">&lt;center&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Siren's last song&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/center&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;by Ebb/Flow Collective&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;Saturday, March 7th, 8pm&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Ocean herself brings an oil-slicked message with the tide.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rainbow plastics fill the siren’s tail as he swims a somber finale, alone in a foreign place he once called home.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The siren’s last song, a distant memory –the Ocean embraces him as he drifts into eternal sleep.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div style=&quot;text-align: center;&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://localhost:4000/img/sirensong.jpeg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;center&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Out of the Dust&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/center&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;by Kirstin Brown and Helen Fitanides&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;Saturday, March 7th, 8pm; and Thursday, March 12th, 8pm&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Out of the Dust explores the fate of creatures living in a world in which they can no longer survive. Starting on the ground, they are forced to adapt to environmental factors outside their control, and eventually must find new habitat for their species survival. This piece embodies the struggle of all beings facing a changing climate and limited resources.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;center&gt;&lt;h3&gt;The Secrets Of The Trees&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/center&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;by Caitlyn Kilgore; featuring Stephanie Chen, Bobbi Dulaney, Carrie Gaydos, and Mel Mark&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;All Dates and Times&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Inspired by the book The Hidden Life of Trees by Peter Wohleben, this piece blossomed into an affirmation of our interdependence. Drawing inspiration from Standing Rock and other political actions, and books like Blessed Unrest and Radical Ecology, the performers have woven together a story of struggle and hope in a harrowing time. Touching on themes of socialism, competition, set-back, and rebirth, The Secrets of the Trees is a circus, dance, and theatrical critique of capitalism and greed told through the eyes of the forest as they struggle for survival in the Anthropocene.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div style=&quot;text-align: center;&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://localhost:4000/img/secretofthetrees.jpeg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Siren's last song by Ebb/Flow Collective Saturday, March 7th, 8pm The Ocean herself brings an oil-slicked message with the tide. Rainbow plastics fill the siren’s tail as he swims a somber finale, alone in a foreign place he once called home. The siren’s last song, a distant memory –the Ocean embraces him as he drifts into eternal sleep. Out of the Dust by Kirstin Brown and Helen Fitanides Saturday, March 7th, 8pm; and Thursday, March 12th, 8pm Out of the Dust explores the fate of creatures living in a world in which they can no longer survive. Starting on the ground, they are forced to adapt to environmental factors outside their control, and eventually must find new habitat for their species survival. This piece embodies the struggle of all beings facing a changing climate and limited resources. The Secrets Of The Trees by Caitlyn Kilgore; featuring Stephanie Chen, Bobbi Dulaney, Carrie Gaydos, and Mel Mark All Dates and Times Inspired by the book The Hidden Life of Trees by Peter Wohleben, this piece blossomed into an affirmation of our interdependence. Drawing inspiration from Standing Rock and other political actions, and books like Blessed Unrest and Radical Ecology, the performers have woven together a story of struggle and hope in a harrowing time. Touching on themes of socialism, competition, set-back, and rebirth, The Secrets of the Trees is a circus, dance, and theatrical critique of capitalism and greed told through the eyes of the forest as they struggle for survival in the Anthropocene.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Fri, Mar 6, 8PM</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2020/03/06/1.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Fri, Mar 6, 8PM" /><published>2020-03-06T20:00:00-08:00</published><updated>2020-03-06T20:00:00-08:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2020/03/06/1</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2020/03/06/1.html">&lt;center&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Terra Femme&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/center&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;AspearmanAndCo.org&quot;&gt;by A. Spearman &amp;amp; Co&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;Friday, March 6th, 8pm&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Terra Femme centers on embodying Earth as a feminine being whose energy (resources-water, land, plants and vegetation, minerals, etc) is being drained by her children who create man made devices and disasters. The dancers and Earth Choir are her children.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A. Spearman &amp;amp; Co. is a contemporary fusion dance company that was founded in 2012 by Artistic Director Andréa Spearman. All artists are trained in various fields of movement including ballet, jazz, hip hop, modern, and cultural dance. This company seeks to design and create unique vocabularies of performance. Explosive and varied, this company maintains it’s loyalty to unusual collaborations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div style=&quot;text-align: center;&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://localhost:4000/img/terrafemme.jpeg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;center&gt;&lt;h3&gt;The Secrets Of The Trees&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/center&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;by Caitlyn Kilgore; featuring Stephanie Chen, Bobbi Dulaney, Carrie Gaydos, and Mel Mark&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;All Dates and Times&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Inspired by the book The Hidden Life of Trees by Peter Wohleben, this piece blossomed into an affirmation of our interdependence. Drawing inspiration from Standing Rock and other political actions, and books like Blessed Unrest and Radical Ecology, the performers have woven together a story of struggle and hope in a harrowing time. Touching on themes of socialism, competition, set-back, and rebirth, The Secrets of the Trees is a circus, dance, and theatrical critique of capitalism and greed told through the eyes of the forest as they struggle for survival in the Anthropocene.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div style=&quot;text-align: center;&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://localhost:4000/img/secretofthetrees.jpeg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Terra Femme by A. Spearman &amp;amp; Co Friday, March 6th, 8pm Terra Femme centers on embodying Earth as a feminine being whose energy (resources-water, land, plants and vegetation, minerals, etc) is being drained by her children who create man made devices and disasters. The dancers and Earth Choir are her children. A. Spearman &amp;amp; Co. is a contemporary fusion dance company that was founded in 2012 by Artistic Director Andréa Spearman. All artists are trained in various fields of movement including ballet, jazz, hip hop, modern, and cultural dance. This company seeks to design and create unique vocabularies of performance. Explosive and varied, this company maintains it’s loyalty to unusual collaborations. The Secrets Of The Trees by Caitlyn Kilgore; featuring Stephanie Chen, Bobbi Dulaney, Carrie Gaydos, and Mel Mark All Dates and Times Inspired by the book The Hidden Life of Trees by Peter Wohleben, this piece blossomed into an affirmation of our interdependence. Drawing inspiration from Standing Rock and other political actions, and books like Blessed Unrest and Radical Ecology, the performers have woven together a story of struggle and hope in a harrowing time. Touching on themes of socialism, competition, set-back, and rebirth, The Secrets of the Trees is a circus, dance, and theatrical critique of capitalism and greed told through the eyes of the forest as they struggle for survival in the Anthropocene.</summary></entry></feed>